https://www.cssportal.com/privacy.php

web site are protected by applicable copyright and
trade mark law.
2. Disclaimer
The materials on CSSPortal.com's web site are
provided "as is". CSSPortal.com makes no warranties,
expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and
negates all other warranties, including without
limitation, implied warranties or conditions of
merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose,
Internet web site or otherwise relating to such
materials or on any sites linked to this site.
consequential or incidental damages, these
limitations may not apply to you.
not, however, make any commitment to update the
materials.
endorsement by CSSPortal.com of the site. Use of any
such linked web site is at the user's own risk.
then current version of these Terms and Conditions
of Use.
General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a
Web Site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us.
Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order
for you to understand how we collect, use,
communicate and disclose and make use of personal
information. The following outlines our privacy
policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal
information, we will identify the purposes for which
information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information
solely with the objective of fulfilling those
purposes specified by us and for other compatible
purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the
individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as
necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and
fair means and, where appropriate, with the
knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for
which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary
for those purposes, should be accurate, complete,
and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable
security safeguards against loss or theft, as well
as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or
modification.
We will make readily available to customers
information about our policies and practices
relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in
accordance with these principles in order to ensure
that the confidentiality of personal information is
protected and maintained.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve
ads when you visit our website. These companies may
use information (not including your name, address,
relation to·not having this information used by
these companies,
click here.
Learn Wordpress
Wordpress hosting. Theme and plugin reviews. Wordpress development tips.
Templatic
Wordpress Themes, Cloud Hosting, Backups and Webmaster Tips.
A2 Web Hosting
Shared hosting, Reseller hosting, Cloud hosting, Dedicated hosting.
Character Codes
Search Over 100,000 Characters. View Emojis.
Web Hosting
Provides information on a range of web hosting companies.
Online Password Manager
Access your passwords from any computer, no need to remember all of your passwords.
Advertise Here
About CSSPortal
CSS Portal is home to many examples of CSS and how it can be used in website design. Here you'll find all CSS properties and many CSS generators to help with all your design needs.
Friends
Expand URL
Whois Search
Password Manager
TLD Search
Website Tools & Generators
CSSPortal
Donate to CSSPortal
Copyright © 2020, CSSPortal.com All rights reserved.
